<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Essays by Danielle Navarro</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Essays by Danielle Navarro</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hidden loss</title>
      <link>/post/hidden-loss/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hidden-loss/</guid>
      <description>On the support we do not offer to the partners of transitioners</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something improbable happened</title>
      <link>/post/something-improbable-happened/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/something-improbable-happened/</guid>
      <description>A story about rape, probability, and statistics. Maybe an attempt to heal old wounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On my fear of gender critical feminism</title>
      <link>/post/gender-critical-fear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gender-critical-fear/</guid>
      <description>Miscellaneous thoughts on why I am frightened by gender critical feminists and their politics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniel</title>
      <link>/post/daniel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/daniel/</guid>
      <description>Slivers of memory</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meaningless questions do not have meaningful answers</title>
      <link>/post/trans-women-are/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/trans-women-are/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t have an opinion about whether trans women are real women, any more than I have an estimate of the number of angels that can dance on the head of a pin or a belief about the mood of Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time to move over</title>
      <link>/post/time-to-move-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/time-to-move-over/</guid>
      <description>A few remarks on my experiences with gender dysphoria, transition, and being the unwilling participant in someone else&amp;rsquo;s culture war; additionally, a resolution to withdraw my voice from a discussion that has done me too much harm already</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A lexical decision</title>
      <link>/post/a-lexical-decision/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/a-lexical-decision/</guid>
      <description>Why do I call myself a woman?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On small differences, academics, and biological sex</title>
      <link>/post/on-small-differences/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/on-small-differences/</guid>
      <description>There is a strange kind of intellectual myopia that academics are vulnerable to whenever the subject of transgender rights comes up. People who might under normal circumstances speak in a careful and measured fashion suddenly become prone to wild exaggeration and reckless generalisations. I am genuinely baffled as to why this happens, but I have some hypotheses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Never the same girl twice</title>
      <link>/post/never-the-same/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/never-the-same/</guid>
      <description>An essay about transitions, changing worlds, and how we sometimes don&amp;rsquo;t notice that things are no longer what they once were.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An ordinary account</title>
      <link>/post/an-ordinary-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/an-ordinary-account/</guid>
      <description>A long piece on transgender rights, in which I admit that I do have opinions on what social and political considerations a person such as myself deserves. The central claim is that transgender rights can be justified on their own terms, pragmatically, without requiring any recourse to strong metaphysical claims about the nature of gender identity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>52 pickup</title>
      <link>/post/52-pickup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/52-pickup/</guid>
      <description>A short, disjointed essay on the strangeness of being a trans woman in academia.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>